It feels too good
気持ち良すぎる
...
Can I walk?
足 していい?
That's stupid...
バカしたやつ...
Mei-chan felt so good that a lot came out...
メイちゃん、気持ち良すぎて、いっぱい出ちゃった...
Well then, let's go wash it once.
じゃあ、一回洗いに行こうか
This too.
これも一緒にね
That's right, let's go once.
そうそう、一回行こう
Let's go, let's go.
行 こう、行こう
Let's go in.
入ろう
I have to commemorate it.
記念しないと
let's go.
行こう
Stop for a moment until you feel like it.
ちょっとお気になるまで止まって
I'm so impressed.
感動めっちゃだよ
Is this okay?
これ大丈夫?
It's a little warm.
ちょっと温かい
warm?
温かい?
TRUE?
本当?
It feels so good...
気持ち良すぎる...
I have to fix it.
取り直さないとね
I have to wash it off properly.
ちゃん と洗い流さないとね
Let me walk your feet this way.
足、こっち歩いてもらう
Talking.
おしゃばり
Should I wash this by applying it?
これ、当てて洗うの?
Feels good
気持ち良
Too...
す ぎる...
It feels too good
気持ち良すぎる
...
It's raining so it feels good
降 りちゃったから気持ち良す
Giru.
ぎ る
Because it's small.
狭いからさ
Let's go, let's go.
行こう、行こう
I'm going.
行っちゃうよ